President reagan:
Air and naval forces
of the United States
Launched a series of strikes
against terrorist facilities...
Reporter:
Pan am flight 103 crashed
into the town of lockerbie.
Reagan:
He has sanctioned
acts of terror
In africa, europe,
the middle east.
President george h.W. Bush:
This will not stand, this
aggression against, uh, kuwait.
Reagan:
This relentless pursuit
of terror.
President george w. Bush:
We will make no distinction...
Reporter:
The uss cole was attacked
While refueling in
the port of aden.
This was an act of terrorism.
It was a despicable
and cowardly act.
The next samba
we're going to swing for you
Is one of the good old
favorites.
...Until something stops him.
Carrie: It was right
in front of my eyes,
And I never saw it coming.
Man: That plane crashed
into the world trade center.
Thousands of people running.
We must and we will remain
vigilant at home and abroad.
(speaking arabic)
Saul: You're the smartest
and the dumbest fucking person
I've ever known.
Carrie:
I'm not the one
who got it wrong.
I'm the only one
who got it right.
Saul:
Take 'em.
Take 'em all.
Previously on homeland...
It wasn't me.
We have to go.
What do you mean?
Go where?
No one else will believe you.
What are we doing here?
Activating
my insurance policy.
A friend, June, will
meet us at the border.
She'll drive us up to montreal
Where we get onto
a fishing boat,
Which takes us up
to newfoundland.
The border's in a few miles.
You're not coming, are you?
I can't now.
Frank:
Have you seen the paper yet?
Cia officer linked
to langley bomber.
The case officer in question,
She's been diagnosed as bipolar.
It's carrie.
She called a reporter.
Apparently she thinks
it's important they quote,
"hear her side
of the story."
The cia gave you
that story to set me up.
For what?
Nicholas brody is
not responsible
For the explosion at langley.
Did saul berenson know
when he testified
Before the senate subcommittee?
Of course he did.
Everything he said was bullshit.
Did you tell anyone
that I was coming here?
We've got a psychiatric
detention order.
You know she's off
her meds, right?
Unless you think
that's a good idea.
You really have to help me.
This is fucking sham!
Saul: Carrie.
I am so sorry.
Fuck...
You, saul.
(vehicle approaching)
(men speaking in spanish)
(yells in spanish)
(yelling in spanish)
(panting)
(engine starts)
(speaking in spanish)
(grunting)
(panting)
(groans)
(speaking spanish)
Shit what happened to him?
Something went wrong.
I assumed.
Um, across the border.
Dios mío.
Esme!
(speaking spanish)
I'm going to take
a look at you now, okay?
Are you a doctor?
(mumbles)
Interesting question.
(brody yelling)
I know.
I know, I know it hurts.
Could someone do something
about the lights?
(speaks spanish)
You've lost a lot of blood.
You're in hypovolemic shock.
We're going to try
to repair the bleeds.
(grunting)
This will help
with the pain.
Enough, enough.
We don't want to stop his heart.
Okay, paco?
I need you
to hold something for me.
Can you do that?
Give me your hand.
And put it right here.
Right... There.
Can you feel it?
Uh-huh.
It's beating-- boom, boom, boom?
Boom, boom, boom.
Yes, yes, yes.
Pinch it. Pinch.
Don't let go.
Where are my lights?
Can't work
with a flickering light.
(speaking in spanish)
Where are my lights?
(grunting)
Well done.
Ah.
Esme?
Will he live?
Depends.
How old were those
antibiotics you got me?
Oh, he'll make it.
He's a strong one.
You know who he is.
Absolutely no idea.
Just an anonymous stranger
With two bullets in his gut.
Though, hypothetically...
I'm-I'm...
I'm wondering.
An american fugitive falls
in your lap.
One with a bounty on his head.
$10 million, dead or alive.
Why go through a world
of trouble to save him...
Instead of just collecting
the reward?
Maybe someone did you
A favor once.
Must be some favor.
(yells)
(groaning)
(speaking in spanish)
Be still.
(grunting)
(sobbing)
No fever.
(speaks spanish)
Yeah, yeah.
Ah, thank you.
Ah, thank... Thank you.
Thanks.
(movement nearby)
(music in the distance)
(grunting)
No!
(speaking spanish)
No, I want to get up.
I want... (groans)
No more.
I can't think.
No more, please.
God.
No.
Will you help me
get up, please?
No. (speaking spanish)
(groans)
(spanish continues)
Need to see.
No.
(groans)
(panting)
(distant singing)
Where am I?
El niño:
Caracas.
Your new home.
You shouldn't be up.
(speaking spanish)
You need to rest.
(spanish continues)
(panting, spanish continues)
You're lucky to be alive,
you know.
Those columbians,
they nearly killed you.
There's a bounty on your head.
I know.
A big one.
You're never safe,
even here with me.
My wallet's missing,
And so is my passport.
Somebody took them.
I couldn't stop him.
I need my passport for travel.
(chuckles)
Don't worry about that.
I can't get another one.
Just-just get better now.
We'll try to find out
who took your things.
(speaking spanish)
Why are you trying
to help me?
You know carrie mathison.
So do I.
Stay here on this floor.
(speaks spanish)
Thank you.
(groans)
(sighing)
(low, indistinct conversations)
Oh, it feels good.
To be walking.
Walking?
Walking.
(groans)
We're walking.
Yes, we're walking.
With a cane.
Bastón.
Bastón?
(indistinct talking)
We're walking with a cane.
(laughter)
Aah!
(music playing distantly)
Agua?
Oh, yes, yeah.
Thanks.
(panting)
Gracias.
(panting continues)
I prescribe rest.
You go gallivanting about.
Paco?
Trekking clear
across the building,
What were you thinking?
Esme?
No.
You sure?
You seem like you're
in a lot of pain.
I'll survive.
Guess you're good
at that, aren't you?
So, what'd you make of it?
What?
What you saw.
This abscess beyond healing
we call home.
They call it the tower of david.
Not for king david,
Heaven forbid.
For david brillembourg,
The particularly
egomaniacal banker
Unfortunately, before
it was completed,
David died.
Then the whole economy died,
Construction stopped,
The squatters all moved in,
And viola.
Scooch.
Well, if you hate it...
Did I say I hate it?
So why are you here?
That's a dangerous question.
"why am I here?"
Leads to "why are you here?"
You see?
We're here
Because the world
outside can be...
Judgmental and cruel?
We're here because this
is the place that accepts us.
We're here
because we belong here.
(sighs)
I'm not staying.
Of course not.
I just need
to get my strength back.
Don't we all
Need to get our strength back?
(banging)
(panting)
(distant singing)
(quietly singing along)
(shouts in spanish)
(spanish continues)
(banging)
(panting)
Come.
Where?
(panting continues)
(horns honking distantly)
Yours.
(sighs)
Thanks.
Is this...
Is this him?
Is this the man
That robbed you?
Is it?
He says he did it.
Yeah, okay, but...
No, no, no, wait, wait a second.
No!
No, no, don't!
(screaming)
get the...
(thuds)
You didn't have to kill him!
No?
No, you didn't.
Fine. (speaks spanish)
We let people rob us,
no problem.
And then what
if they recognize you
With ten million dollars
on your head?
What stops them from saying,
"I know where he is."
Hmm?
Back to your room.
(speaking spanish)
Esme:
Where you go?
Somewhere else.
Do you have money?
I need money.
Dinaro?
Dinaro!
Do you have any?
Don't go.
I can't stay here.
(indistinct conversations,
music playing)
(man shouting)
You stop!
I'm going out.
(gun cocks)
I need to leave.
Go out there.
I need to get out of here.
El niño:
Where?
Where you think you go?
Out.
Out... Out where?
To the next place.
I've been taken from
one place to the next.
From here to there
to here...
You were nearly killed.
I can't stay here.
Why?
It's...
It's not good enough?
No, I didn't mean that.
Not, not good enough for you?
Huh? (laughs)
Oh, I guess it's
because of that-that thief?
He... He upset you?
Look...
I appreciate all you've
done for me, okay?
But I'm better now.
What does that mean?
Means I can make it on my own.
I just need to get
to the next place.
There's no next place.
What? There has to be.
No.
Does carrie know I'm here?
Does she?
No one can know.
We have to tell her.
I call her on the phone?
Huh?
No, I didn't mean that.
A postcard then?
Or we just call the cia,
They give us $10 million--
split it, eh... Even steven?
I tell you last time,
Where you are,
carrie doesn't want to know.
This is it for you.
End of the line.
El niño thinks
you're an ingrate.
I assured him
you're just confused.
But he's right, you know.
This is your home.
It isn't easy to accept--
Believe me, I know.
Not how you pictured yourself.
There must be some mistake,
and on and on.
The voices in your head are
not your friends right now.
You have to make them go away.
The germans who invented it...
...Had a special name
for a medicine
Powerful enough to do just that.
"hero-isch."
"heroic."
The drug is.
So you don't have to be.
Get out.
Come, paco.
Come, come.
I slept six whole hours
yesterday.
I can't remember the last
time that happened, so...
Yeah, all things considered,
I feel pretty damn lucid.
And you're drinking
enough water?
I think so.
Any headaches?
They'll go away.
This isn't my first time
Acclimating to lithium,
you know?
Dizzy spells?
One or two.
Nothing unbearable.
I was wondering if you could
tell saul berenson
How much better I'm doing.
What... Makes you think
I'm in touch with saul berenson?
We both know who you're writing
those notes for.
You think I'm reporting back
to the cia?
I know you are.
And that's fine.
Just...
Tell saul
I'm sorry I fucked up.
It won't happen again.
What do you mean
you fucked up?
I mean...
I went off my meds.
Clearly, that was a bad idea.
You told dr. Harlan
your meds dulled you.
Well, maybe that's not
such a bad thing.
This is quite
the sea change for you.
(sighs)
After three weeks
in here, it's...
Hard to hold on to any grudges.
So saul did you a favor
putting you in the hospital.
Yes.
Removing you from
a delusional relationship.
With a suspected
terrorist, no less.
That was his testimony,
wasn't it?
It was.
You're saying that
was the right thing to do?
Yes.
And you honestly
believe that?
Carrie...
I want you to answer truthfully.
I want you to recover.
From what?
We both know I'm not here
because I'm crazy.
I'm here because they don't
know where else to put me.
No one said you were crazy.
Well, no one had to.
I'm in a fucking psych ward.
Look...
(sighs)
The sooner I can talk to saul,
the sooner I can go home
And you can go back to doing
something useful with your life.
W-what are you writing?
I was out of line just then.
I'm sorry. I...
You want to earn
your visiting privileges,
You'll have to be a bit
more cooperative than that.
I know.
And then there's the question of
the efficacy of your medication.
All right, I'm sorry, I just...
Will you please tell saul
that I'm better?
(grunting quietly)
Esme:
Hey...
They see you.
You can't do that.
I have to.
No...
He know.
He know what happened.
Listen. Stop.
(men speaking spanish
in distance)
Please...
I can't stay here.
I can't.
I have to leave.
I have to go out there.
I can't live here.
(speaking spanish)
Aquì.
No   aquì.
(panting)
I'll die here.
No place to go.
There is a place.
There is.
There is...
There is somewhere to go.
No. My father say...
There is a place.
The mosque.
Will you help me?
Well, well...
That's really quite something.
Is that a little balcony?
It is, yeah.
It's just darling.
Thanks.
Mike, sarah--
come look at this.
Isn't that lovely?
Look at all the detail.
Can I use the restroom?
Of course.
Jim, why don't you put
some paint on that?
Carrie, are you in here?
Yeah, I'm fine...
What, what...
I needed to get
out of there.
...What happened?
Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
You're...
I just had to get
out of there.
...Bleeding.
What?
Oh, shit.
Honey, if you are hurting
yourself, I need to know.
No, I said I'm fine.
I know, carrie,
what you said.
Let me see.
Look, I had a bad moment--
that's all.
I'm-I'm taking my lithium.
(voice breaking):
I'm going to group.
I'm doing everything
that's asked of me.
I'm... Okay. Okay.
(crying)
that's it. That's it.
Okay?
That's all right.
It's all right now.
Okay, that's all right.
(carrie sobs)
Please don't tell.
Okay.
(sobs quietly)
(stall door bangs shut)
(conversing in spanish)
So promise me this will
not happen again.
I promise.
Because, if it does...
It won't.
I was just frustrated.
Okay. When I get frustrated,
I take a deep breath
and I count to ten.
Hey, carrie,
keep your head up.
It's not like they're
going to forget you in here.
Someone's already
come by to check on you.
Who?
I'm not sure.
What, you didn't get his name?
Nope. He didn't say.
He asked about you,
how you're doing.
We don't
tell 'em anything.
Well, if he comes again,
let me know.
I need to see him.
Okay, as soon as you're
granted visiting privileges...
No. Sooner than that.
It's saul. Has to be.
Okay, honey,
Let's get you back
to group, okay?
Will you promise me?
Carrie, I've already
risked my job once.
And this is the last favor
I'll ask. I mean it.
(sighs)
People see you.
They know.
Oh, the imam
won't turn me in.
He'll help me.
I'm a muslim.
Me...
Me muslim.
See? Refuge.
Esme:
Refugio.
Perfecto.
(sighs)
Take me with you.
What? No.
You can't leave me here.
No, I can't take you with me.
No, I...
Oh, god, I'm sorry.
I can't.
I can't. I...
I'm sorry.
Salaam alaykum.
Alaykum salaam.
(brody speaking arabic)
(speaking arabic)
Someone's here to see me.
I need an elevator key.
If you could just
wait in the rec room.
No, I have a visitor.
I have to see him.
You're still not
on the list.
Please?
He's waiting for me.
I need you to calm down.
I am calm.
Where's abby?
She's on break.
Well, will you go get her?
Because he's
going to leave soon.
Okay, now, let's
talk about this.
Jesus. Where the fuck is abby?
What's going on here?
Oh, thank god.
Someone's here to see me.
He's downstairs.
All right, all right.
I-I'll handle this.
We'll take her back
to her room.
Come on. Let's go.
It's saul.
I saw him
through the window.
Keep your voice down.
(shower running)
(sighs)
(grunting and groaning)
(panting)
You're not a muslim.
You are a terrorist.
(gasping)
(imam's wife screaming)
Brody:
No, no, no.
Don't! What are you doing?
Saul?
Hi.
Who are you?
Paul franklin.
What happened to your head?
Uh, I-I fell.
Did saul send you?
No. I'm pretty sure he wouldn't
approve of my being here.
I'm an associate
at bennett, parr and hamilton.
We're a law firm.
Yeah, I know.
I've heard of you.
Is there anywhere we could speak
a little more privately?
(speaking spanish)
Esme.
(door closes)
(grunting and groaning)
I told you, don't leave.
But you go.
This... This is
what happens.
We all get trouble.
So now you stay here.
(speaks spanish)
This is your new home.
You will eat here, sleep here,
shit here, die here.
Carrie won't save you.
No one will.
Understand?
Do you understand me?
Yes.
And you stay away
from my daughter.
You stay away.
(speaks spanish)
Graham:
Been a naughty boy.
Naughty, naughty boy.
Paul:
I heard you had
a difficult hearing.
Carrie:
"difficult" doesn't
really cover it.
So we both know you could
be here for quite a while.
One of our partners
would like to meet with you.
Well, he knows
where to find me.
I don't think
you understand.
I'm talking about
getting you out of here.
You could do that?
Why would you
want to help me?
As I said, I'm here
on behalf of a partner.
And what does he want?
Simply to talk to you.
About?
Whatever it is,
It's important enough
that he sent me.
Look, I know
how that sounds.
In your position,
I'd be paranoid, too.
You don't know the first
thing about my position.
I know you don't
belong here.
That you're not
actually crazy.
And I know you
want nothing more
Than to get out
and go home.
Carrie...
I'm on your side.
Are you all right?
(laughs)
I'm just... I'm
trying to remember
Where I've heard
that line before.
What line?
"I'm on your side."
I know what
you're doing.
What do you mean?
I mean I'm a case officer.
I used to recruit
assets for a living.
This isn't like that.
Isn't it?
No, you think
I'm vulnerable.
Not at all.
No, worse than that:
You think I'm weak,
And maybe, with just
the right incentive,
I'll turn against the
people who did this to me.
Well, I'm
telling you no.
So whoever the hell it
is you're working for--
The syrians, the israelis,
the iranians--
You tell them that.
You tell them I would
rather die in here.
You're not
seeing this clearly.
Yeah, which part
did I get wrong?
(indistinct broadcast over tv)
Meds.
Abby:
Carrie?
Are you all right?
I need my meds.
Graham:
What are we going
to do with you?
I can't stay here.
Of course you can.
It's like the hole in iraq.
I can't do it again.
Well, I'm sure
you'll find a way.
Everywhere you go,
Other people die,
But you always
manage to survive.
Have you noticed that?
You're like a cockroach,
Still there after the last
nuclear bombs go off.
You belong here.
Am I right?
(sighs)
Come on.
(lock clicking)
(grunting)
(panting)
Captioned by
media access group at wgbh
access.Wgbh.Org