m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
人人影视\NYYeTs.com
■
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译\N禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
翻译：冰蓝    Hannah    叉烧包    小花豆    北湾    喃喃
■
时间轴：小萌    贝壳    后期：冰河   校对&监制：非燕
星  恋\N第一季 第一集
2014年9月17日
是我们抵达地球的日子\NThe day we arrived.
我们从一个濒临灭亡的星球逃离\NWe fled a dying planet.
我们的飞船迫降在这里\NOur ship crash-landed here.
对于我们来说  这应是解放日\NFor my kind
避难日\NRefuge.
但是对于地球人来说\NBut for everyone on Earth...
这却是侵略\Nit was an invasion.
人类让我们别无选择  只能自我防卫\NThe humans left us no choice but to defend ourselves.
弹药来袭\NIncoming!
快跑  快跑
快跑
我听从了父亲的吩咐\NI did as my father said.
我奋力飞奔\NI ran as fast as my legs would carry me
不知道自己在逃避什么\Nnot understanding what I was running from.
更不确定我在奔向什么\NAnd less sure what I was running to.
国民警卫队继续\NNational Guardsmen continue
和外星人进行一场流血冲突\Nto engage in a bloody conflict with the alien species
他们的飞船坠落在巴吞鲁日外的几公里处\Nwhose ship crashed to Earth several miles from Baton Rouge.
总统宣称进入紧急状态\NThe president has issued a state of emergency.
而官方人士报告  一些侵略者\NWhile officials report that some of the invaders
已经被包围\Nhave been rounded up
侵略者袭击  伤亡人数增加
可能有些外星人逃脱了追捕\Nit's possible some may have eluded capture.
你觉得外星人的计划是什么\NWhat do you think would be the alien plan?
我们该去我母亲家\NWe should go to my mother's.
道路封锁了\NThe roads are closed.
而且  去了那边情况也不会好转\NAnd plus
尽量放松吧\NJust try and relax.
怎么了  爸爸\NWhat's wrong
没事  宝贝\NNothing
一切都很好\NEverything's fine.
别忘了吃药  埃默里\NDon't forget to take your medicine
好的  爸爸\NOkay
刚刚传来的消息  航空航天局的天文学家推断\NJust getting word; NASA astronomers have speculated
这艘宇宙飞船的轨道\Nthat the trajectory of the spacecraft
起源于一个名叫奥特里安的遥远的太阳系\Noriginated from a distant solar system called Atria.
不管他们从何而来\NRegardless of where they came from
当地居民和世界领导都很担心其意图\Nlocal residents and world leaders are wary of their intentions.
有人吗\NHello?
没事的  没事的\NIt's okay. It's okay.
你也是外星人  对吧\NYou're one of them
我马上回来\NI'll be right back.
另一方面  如果\NIf
他们的目标实为征服并占领地球\Ntheir goal was actual occupation and conquest
那他们可能会优先考虑那些...\Nthen they would probably have to prioritize anything...
没事的\NIt's okay.
你看起来不像个怪物\NYou don't look like a monster.
你今晚可以待在这里\NYou can stay here tonight.
我早晨再来看你\NI'll come see you in the morning.
别出声\NBe very quiet.
很好吃  对吧\NIt's good
给  用叉子\NHere. Use the fork.
这个叫星星\NThis one's called star.
从这里穿过\NThrough here.
从里面穿过\NThrough the loop.
松开  就是颗星星  你来试试\NLet go
B小队1-7\NBravo unit one-seven...
得把你藏起来\NWe've got to hide you.
他在这里\NHe's in here!
快上  快上\NGo
离她远点\NGet away from her!
别伤害他\NDon't hurt him!
-快  -不要\N- Now! - No!
十年后
十年前  名叫奥特里安人的\NIt's been ten years since the alien species
外星物种抵达地球\Nknown as the Atrians arrived on Earth
美国军方将其包围\Nand the U.S. Military rounded them up
将他们送入一处政府辖区\Nand put them in a government facility
一直关押到现在\Nwhere they remained in lockdown.
今天  在尝试将他们融入社会的争议中\NToday
七名奥特里安青少年会成为马歇尔高中的学生\Nseven Atrian teens will become students at Marshall High School.
备受争议的取消七名奥特里安\N青少年隔离的计划
小朱\NHey
埃默里\NHey
只有你才能在早上七点展现大汗淋漓的性感\NOnly you could pull off sweaty sexy at 7:00 A.M.
在马歇尔高中外面  愤怒的抗议者要求\NOutside Marshall High
奥特里安人继续被关押在他们的隔离区\Nthat the Atrians remain sequestered inside their sector.
马歇尔高中实况\N愤怒的抗议仍在继续
该做拉伸运动了  来吧\NTime to stretch. Come on.
我的前任病友现在成了我的私人教练\NMy former hospital buddy's now my personal trainer.
你说过一直想要一个的\NYou said you always wanted one.
是啊  名字叫费尔南多\NYeah. Named Fernando.
或者特里斯坦\NOr Tristan.
他有外国口音  还有腹肌\NWith an accent and abs.
这些反对消除隔离的拥护者相信奥特里安人\NThese anti-integration advocates believe the Atrians
抗议者要求了解\N奥特里安人隐瞒了什么
也许心怀鬼胎  想把地球变为殖民地\Nmay be hiding a greater plan to colonize Earth.
如果要问我  这整个隔离计划\NIf you ask me
只不过是为了分散大家的注意力\Nis just a distraction from the real issue.
-每个频道都在放这个吗  -对\N- Is this on every channel? - Yep.
市民对消除隔离的反应
那艘飞船在整座小镇上投下了阴影\NThat ship is casting a shadow over this whole town...
疯子们今天都出来了\NAll the loonies are out today.
真是不得不爱阴谋论者啊\NYou got to love conspiracy theorists.
有一个人声称奥特里安人\NOne of them was claiming that the Atrians
在隔离区里种植了一种草药  名叫柏草\Ngrow a medicinal herb inside their Sector called cyper.
能治疗阴谋论者吗\NCan it cure conspiracy theorists?
我只是说\NI'm just saying.
也许你可以和一个奥特里安人搞好关系\NMaybe you could get chummy with one of the Atrians.
拿到一批柏草\NGet a batch.
拯救这整所医院\NFix up this whole hospital.
我怎么说的\NWhat did I say?
怀特希尔指挥官
让他们后退\NKeep these guys back.
天啊  是你爸爸\NOh
如你所见  隔离区执法队的雷·怀特希尔指挥官\NAs you can see
怀特希尔指挥官
扫描了七名奥特里安人的腕带\Nscans the wristbands of the Atrian Seven
这样他们在学校里时  当局就能追踪其位置\Nallowing authorities to track their location while at school.
他真走运\NHe's so lucky.
他是为数不多真正可以说\NHe's
去过隔离区的人\Nthat they've been inside the Sector.
当然只有你才会认为那是走运\NOf course only you would consider that lucky.
七名奥特里安人离开隔离区
那你对今天觉得紧张吗\NSo
当然觉得\NYeah. Sure.
昨晚新闻里的那个人说着\NI mean
全世界都会关注马歇尔高中\Nhow the eyes of the world would be on Marshall High.
七名奥特里安人离开隔离区
让你四年后重返学校的第一天\NLeave it to you to start your first day back at school after four years
就被全世界关注\Nin front of the eyes of the world.
向政府施压\N...are putting pressure on our government.
媒体没有进行全面报道\NThe media hasn't covered it thoroughly enough...
真高兴你病情好转了  小埃\NI'm really glad you got better
谢谢你\NThanks.
轮到你了\NNow it's your turn.
奥特里安七名青少年正前往马歇尔高中\NThe Atrian Seven are now headed to Marshall High
那里的反对者越来越多\Nwhere protests continue to grow.
我代表所有特区政府的同事们\NI speak for all my colleagues in D.C.
通过将近三年的不断讨论\NWhen I say that after three years of ongoing discussion
我们很荣幸  终于实现了这个项目\Nwe're very proud to see this program finally come to fruition.
如果这一项目成功的话\NA program which
可以让所有奥特里安人融入社会\Ncould lead to the integration of all Atrians into society.
我们希望我们不仅能够和平共处\NThe hope is that we're not just able to peacefully coexist
还能互相学习\Nbut we also learn from one another.
他们的文化\NTheir culture alone...
那些歪星人不属于这里\NThose Tatties belong with their own kind!
这属于我们的孩子们\NOur kids were raised right.
放开我  放开我\NGet off of me. Get off of me!
歪星人  滚回家\NTatties
走吧  咱们四处转转\NCome on
科学实验室里有一些被编号的猴子\NIn the tech lab are code monkeys.
就好像是这个奇怪的世界\NIt's kind of like this weird world
被一些什么猴子啦猩猩啦统治了\Ndominated by chimps and orangutans or whatever--
他们还不知道怎么和人交流\Nhas no idea how to communicate with humans.
如果你看一眼\NAnd if you look discreetly
你两点钟方向  亚洲时尚达人\Nto your two o'clock: Asian fashionistas.
他们同样的衣服从来不穿两次\NThey never wear the same thing twice.
看楼上  二楼平台上\NAnd further up the stairs
是列宁崇拜者\Nare the Lenin worshipers.
是那个共产主义列宁\NThe Communist Lenin
不是披头士的那个\Nnot the Beatle.
你第一节什么课  英语文学吗\NWhat's your first class? English lit?
但愿你没选特克先生的课\NI hope you didn't get Mr. Turk.
他会让你读《耸肩的阿特拉斯》\NI mean
总之一句话\NAnd let's just say
它的课特别沉闷\Nthat it is a total
特别沉闷  小埃\NIt's a downer
然后我肯定你没有听我说话\Nand I'm so sure that you're not even listening to me.
-小埃  -我听着呢\N- Em! - Yes
你刚刚说特别沉闷\NYou said it's a total and utter downer.
他们来了\NThey're here.
滚吧\NGet out of here!
滚回家\NGo home!
滚回家  滚回家\NGo home! Go home!
都下车\NEverybody off.
好了  跟我来\NAll right
来吧  快点\NLet's go. Move it.
排好队  排成一排  肩并肩站好\NLine it up
到这里排好\NI want a line right here.
快排好\NLine it up.
成一直线\NForm a line.
在这儿排  你  站这里\NRight here along. You. Right here.
今天还能再疯狂一点吗\NI mean
刚才不就是吗\NI think it just did.
我叫格洛丽亚\NMy name is Gloria.
你们不认识我  但我熟悉你们每个人\NYou don't know me
[外星语]
没错  泰瑞  我最近是和人上床了\NYes
并且在马歇尔高中只能说英语\NAnd English is the language of choice here at Marshall High.
你们已经简单学习了礼仪\NI know you've been briefed on protocol
通过了MHS入学考试\Nand passed your MHS entrance exams
但是我认为有必要讲点规矩\Nbut I think it's necessary to set some ground rules
为了你们的安全着想\Nfor your own safety.
想必你们已经注意到增设的安全设施\NI'm sure you've noticed increased security.
我们不希望有任何暴力事件\NWe don't anticipate any violence
这些警卫是为了保护你们\Nbut the guards are here for your protection.
和奥特里安人\NAnd the Atrians.
警卫被批准使用震慑枪\NThe guards have been authorized to use their temblor guns
如果你们走出警戒线\Nif you step out of line.
你们只能离开隔离区去上学\NYou are only permitted to leave the Sector for school.
宵禁仍然存在\NCurfew still stands.
每晚必须在10点前回去\NBack in your pods by 10:00 p.m. every night.
在学校里面  他们和你们一样\NBehind the walls of this school
他们也是学生\NThey're students.
你们是实验对象\NYou're test subjects.
至少现在是\NAt least for the time being.
但是总有一天  你们可以从这里毕业\NBut one day
去上大学  或者工作\NHeading off to college or out in the work force.
想一下  这个项目有可能成功\NImagine the possibilities if this program is a success.
但是这很不容易\NBut it won't be easy.
很多人都希望你们会失败\NA lot of people are hoping you fail.
他们认为你们就是来毁灭我们的\NThey think your race has come here to destroy us.
你们要证明他们说错了\NIt's up to you to prove them wrong.
真希望咱们是那种拿着镭射枪的外星人\NWish we were the kind of aliens who carried ray guns.
还记得咱们在隔离区学校的第一天吗\NRemember our first day at the Sector School?
你们也不喜欢那里\NYou guys hated it there
在那咱们至少不用担心震慑枪\NAt least we didn't have to worry about temblor guns pointed at our heads.
或者更糟的  合唱团\NOr worse. Glee club.
咱们的柜子还被做了标记\NThey tagged our lockers.
右手\NRight.
你得用右手按\NYou got to use your right hand.
对了\NYes.
我发誓我用高科技产品不经常这么差劲的\NI swear I'm not usually this technologically inept.
这没什么\NIt's okay.
你第一天表现得不错\NYou get a pass on your first day.
你从哪转来的\NWhere you transferring from?
我不是转学来的\NOh
我只是过去四年\NI've just been out.
一直在外面\NFor the last four years.
我去年从纽霍尔转来的\NI transferred last year from Newhall.
我也没参加迎新会什么的\NAnd I'm not on the welcoming committee or anything
但我对这挺熟的  如果你需要什么帮忙\Nbut I know my way around
谢谢你\NThanks.
教我用手指\NFor the finger tip.
我是指教我开柜子的方法\NI mean
回见  再见\NSee you. Bye.
我从来没想过我会这么说\NI never thought I'd say this
但是我已经开始想念隔离区学校了\Nbut I'm already starting to miss our Sector School.
人类就是野蛮人\NHumans are savages
无一例外  罗曼\NRoman
是吧\NRight?
对  没错\NYeah. Right.
我宣誓忠实于美利坚合众国国旗\NI pledge allegiance to the flag of the United of America
忠实于她所代表的合众国\Nand to the republic
苍天之下一个无可分割的国家\None nation
在这里  人人享有自由与正义\Nwith liberty and justice for all.
好了\NAll right.
我将发给你们这个学期的课程表\NI'll be passing out your syllabus for the semester.
自己留一份  然后往后传\NTake one and pass it back.
据说他们有三个鸡鸡\NRumor is they have three penises.
小号  中号  还有超大号\NSmall
没错  她是泰勒  甜美  大姐大\NYep. Taylor. Sweet girl
记得中学时代吧\NRemember in middle school?
她现在掌权了\NYeah
掌什么权\NIn charge of what?
所有一切\NAll of it.
你听说过奥特里安人\NHey
可能在隔离区种了一种药草吗\Nthe Atrians supposedly grow in the Sector?
好像叫"柏草"\NSomething called "Cyper"?
据说这种药草有魔力\NIt's
柏草  没听说过\NCyper? No.
不过你要是指大麻\NBut if it's herbs you seek
说不定瘾君子的柜子里有\Nsome of the stoners probably have some in their lockers.
你们吃我们的食物  穿我们的衣服\NYou eat our food
呼吸我们的空气  却不愿对我们的国旗宣誓\Nbreathe our air
我们不是地球公民\NWe're not citizens.
没错  你们是火星人\NOh
实际上  火星人是火星来的\NWell
我们的星球要高级多了\NWe're from a far superior planet.
你说什么  怪胎\NWhat did you say to me
到此为止\NHey
奥特里安人不需要对国旗宣誓\NAtrians are not required to pledge to the flag.
振作点\NCheer up.
你们的自由和正义  我们不会夺去\NYou get to keep liberty and justice all to yourself.
打开秋季学期日程表\NOpen up the fall semester calendar.
有些重要活动\NWe have some events coming up.
诺克斯  你一直极力主张奥特里安人\NNox
与地球人享有平等权利\Nfor equal rights.
你真的认为会有这么一天\NDid you think this day would ever come?
我一直充满希望\NI never lost that hope.
这个项目是迈向种族统一的第一步\NThis program is the first step toward unifying our races.
我无比自豪\NAnd I couldn't be prouder
因为我自己的孩子参与了这历史性的一刻\Nthat my own children are part of history in the making.
-谢谢  先生  -谢谢你\N- Thank you
奥特里安隔离区 - 东门
这是奥特里安七人组  我们过去\NIt's the Atrian Seven! Let's go!
感觉怎样\NHey. How did it go?
很好  跟我们在隔离区受到的凌辱相比\NExcellent. We've been far too insulated in the Sector
这里的人们善良多了\Nfrom just how kind and compassionate these people can be.
你哥现在已经\NYour brother has mastered
深谙地球人的幽默艺术了\Nthe earthly art of sarcasm with relative ease.
说来听听  如果我有幸交到人类朋友\NTell me about it. If I have any chance of making friends
我就装作不认识他了\NI'm gonna have to distance myself from him.
为什么要跟人类做朋友\NWhy do you want to be friends with them?
人类比咱们有趣多了\NHumans are so much more colorful.
抱歉  但今天哪里有趣了\NI'm sorry. What about today was colorful?
是武装警卫还是抗议者\NWas it the armed guards or the protestors?
还是  我知道了  是憎恨我们的同学\NOr...? Oh
他们只是还不了解我们\NThey just don't know us yet.
[外星语]
玛雅  讲英文\NMaia
你们是去那里学习  不是交朋友的\NYou're there to learn
明天又是新的一天\NWell
你女儿自己会解释\NYour daughter will tell you exactly why
她为什么咽不下虾球捞面\Nshe's not devouring that shrimp lo mein.
没什么\NIt's nothing.
我今天一直在想那个躲在棚屋里的男孩\NI just... was thinking a lot about that boy in the shed today.
想他什么\NWhat about him?
想如果他没有要保护我\NAbout how
现在应该还活着\Nhe'd still be alive.
不是所有人都能获救  宝贝\NNot everyone can be saved
有时  要顾全大局\NSometimes... there's a greater plan at work.
用餐愉快\NEnjoy your meal.
下午好  奥特里安人\NGood afternoon
你的午餐选择为爆米花蛋糕\NYour lunch option is puffed rice cake.
你要鸡肉味  牛肉味  还是胡萝卜味\NWould you like chicken-flavored
用餐愉快\NEnjoy your meal.
你叫埃默里  对吧\NIt's Emery
你住在伍德格伦\NYou live over on Woodglen?
-是的  -手机拿出来\N- Yeah. - Let me see your phone.
我们要在这个废弃农舍开派对\NThere's a party at this abandoned farmhouse.
你也来吧\NYou should come.
我可以带卢卡斯吗\NCan I bring Lukas?
当然  如果你们俩是一对的话\NSure
-我们是朋友  -好\N- We're friends. - Oh
因为格雷森不确定\NBecause Grayson wasn't sure.
格雷森要约我吗\NGrayson... was... asking?
我来跟你换班\NI am relieving you of duties.
好  你来得刚好\NYes
那个大姐大要做什么\NSo
你怎么会受到邀请  小埃\NHow did you manage this
是她邀请我的  我们俩\NShe invited me. Or us.
她肯定爱上你了  卢克\NI think she's got a crush on you
不错啊  小埃  你真会哄人开心\NThat's cute
这是你的才能吧  很好\NWas that your material? Great.
好\NOkay.
这是你的社团\NThis is your club?
是的\NYeah.
就是去本地的医院\NYou go to local hospitals
陪病人画画  做剪贴\Nspend time with patients
诸如此类\Nthat sort of thing.
我觉得很抚慰人心\NI found it really comforting.
你去年是社团成员\NYou were in the club last year?
不是  我当时是病人\NNo. I was a patient.
过去四年由于免疫缺陷\NI spent the last four years in the hospital
我一直在住院\Nbecause of an immune deficiency.
那你更喜欢哪个\NSo
画画还是做剪贴\NThe painting or the scrapbooking?
做剪贴\NThe scrapbooking.
谁都可以参加吗\NSo anyone can join?
要占用很多课余时间\NIt's a lot of after-school hours
你们有宵禁令  也不准出隔离区\Nand with your curfew and not being permitted outside the Sector...
我是说  不准私自出隔离区\NI mean
不用说了  我懂  我懂\NNo
我的记忆存储在另一台电脑上\NMy memories are stored on a separate computer anyway
我可能不适合做剪贴\Nso I probably wouldn't be good at scrapbooking.
开玩笑的\NJoking.
还是谢了\NThanks anyway.
喜欢搭讪地球女孩啊  歪星人\NYou like talking to our girls there
很漂亮吧\NYou think they're pretty?
我是想加入她的社团  她没同意\NI was interested in joining her club
不用替我遗憾\NNo
还好没成\NIt's just as well.
我也没什么艺术骨头[细胞]\NI don't have an artistic bone in my body.
你全身上下有骨头吗\NDo you have any bones in your body?
说得好\NGood point.
我们的骨骼系统\NOur
由一万条蜈蚣手拉手组成\Nof 10
不过那是奥特里安人的145号秘密\Nbut that's Atrian secret number 145.
你怎么知道的\NHow do you know that?
-一切都好吗  罗曼  -没事\N- Everything okay
我们只是在互相了解\NWe're just getting to know each other.
我不在乎你爸爸是奥特里安人里的大人物\NI don't care that your dad is some big Atrian honcho.
你在这里就要遵守我们的规矩\NYou play by our rules here.
明白了吗  怪胎\NGot it
-得了吧  -泰瑞\N- Come on... - Teri.
明白了\NGot it.
等等  他们因为你跟\NSo
奥特里安人说话而大发雷霆\Nbecause you talked to an Atrian?
我想这有点像是所有人最糟糕的噩梦\NI mean
什么\NWhat is?
人类和奥特里安之间的恋爱倾向\NThe notion of the human-Atrian hookup.
"恋爱"  我们在谈论\NA "Hookup." Okay
绘画和剪贴\Npainting and scrapbooking.
恋爱都是这样开始的\NThat's how it begins.
我认为得给你找一个新的爱好\NI think we need to find you a new hobby
像是吹制玻璃  肚皮舞也可以\Nlike glassblowing
比如...\NSomething like...
这些是什么\NWhat are these?
出院表\NDischarge forms.
你要回家了\NYou're going home?
不回来了\NFor good?
没错\NYeah.
星期二\NTuesday.
你没有跟我说这件事\NA-And you didn't tell me?
化疗不管用\NThe chemo isn't working.
而且找到一个匹配的骨髓\NAnd finding a bone marrow match
也需耗费数年\Ncould take years.
那么你为什么要回家\NSo
我有贫血症\NI'm anemic.
我每隔一周就会得肺炎\NI'm getting pneumonia every other week.
我的血小板数目不停减少\NMy platelet count keeps dropping.
小朱  你不能就这么放弃了\NJules
这不是放弃的问题\NIt's not about giving up.
我一点都不在乎做检查\NI don't even care about the poking
针扎还有呕吐\Nand the prodding and the puking.
我再也承受不了的是\NWhat I can't take anymore
看见我的父母重燃希望\Nis seeing my parents get their hopes up...
却因为一次次的\Nonly to have them dashed
全血细胞数目测试结果而破灭\None lousy CBC test after another.
他们允许你外出一小时的  对吧\NThey'll let you out for an hour
怎么了  我们要去哪里\NWhy? Where are we going?
你确定你知道这个柏草长什么样吗\NAnd you're sure you know what this cyper herb looks like?
-确定  -很好\N- Yes. - Good.
因为我爸绝对不会轻饶我偷了他的通行证\N'Cause my dad will kill me for stealing his access badge.
隔离区执法队\N雷·怀特希尔
[外星语]
要手镯吗\NAh. Bracelets?
-好吧  我买三个  -不用了  谢谢\N- Okay. I'll take three. - Oh
-朱莉娅  不要买  -不用了  谢谢\N- Julia
看看这是谁来了\NWhat do we have here?
你们这些孩子知道不该来到这里的\NYou kids know you're not supposed to be here.
你有柏草吗\NDo you have any cyper?
柏草\NCyper.
跟我来\NRight here.
走吧\NCome on.
[外星语]
一级防范禁闭\NLockdown.
此隔离区现在正在封锁\NThis Sector is now under lockdown!
快走  快走  快走\NCome on
-跟我走  -好的\N- Let's go. - Okay.
一级防范禁闭\NLockdown!
我们在这里是安全的\NWe'll be safe up here.
小朱  你还好吗\NJules
你在跟我开玩笑吗\NAre you kidding?
这真是太不可思议了\NThat was amazing.
你们俩来这里干什么\NWhat are you guys doing here?
我们来找你们的柏草\NWe came for your cyper.
那你为什么不直接说就好了\NWell
我猜它的疗效已经不再只是我们族群之间的秘密了\NI guess its curative powers are no longer just our secret.
快过来\NCome on.
我们从太空船上偷偷带了一些种子进隔离区\NWe smuggled some seeds into the Sector from our ship.
-这是什么地方  -我和我爸一起建造的\N- What is this place? - My dad and I built it.
这儿有点像是我们的私人避难所\NIt's kind of like our own private sanctuary.
就在这里\NHere it is.
天哪  这里有好多柏草\NWow
想拿多少就拿多少吧\NTake as much as you'd like.
这真的是柏草吗\NIs this really cyper?
没错\NYep.
货真价实\NIt's really cyper.
或者是按照你们的说法\NOr
藏红花\Nsaffron.
藏红花\NSaffron?
我们是这么看待它的\NWell
我们用它来做饭\NWe use it for cooking.
但是一些胆大的警卫吹嘘我们香料的神奇功效\NBut some enterprising guards have made a good amount of cash
卖给在隔离区外容易上当受骗的人类\Nselling our spice's magic remedy to...
赚了一大票\Ngullible humans outside the Sector.
这总是值得一试的\NIt was worth a shot.
你有一个患病的朋友吗\NDo you... have a sick friend?
我没有\NUm
她有\NShe does.
对不起\NI'm sorry.
这也不能算是一无所获\NHey
至少我看到了这个地方\NAt least I got to see this place.
我对于奥特里安人的所有东西都很喜欢\NI'm... obsessed with all things Atrian.
你冷得直发抖  给你\NYou're shivering. Here.
谢谢\NThanks.
真有骑士风度\NSo chivalrous.
城市从这上面看好美\NCity looks beautiful from up here.
你这条疤怎么来的\NHow did you get that scar?
这是很久之前的事了\NIt... it happened a long time ago.
我们抵达地球的那天\NOn Arrival Day.
当时在那个棚屋的人是你  对吧\NThat was you i-in the shed
你一直都知道\NYou knew this whole time.
怎么知道的\NHow?
我在学校见到你的那一瞬间\NThe moment I saw you at school
我就产生了这种\NI had this...
对冷掉的意大利面条的异乎寻常的渴望\Nbizarre craving for cold spaghetti.
但是我很确定你已经死了\NBut I was sure you were dead.
我亲眼看到他们射死了你\NI saw them carry you away.
是差点死掉\NI came close.
我的一个心脏确实停跳了\NOne of my hearts actually stopped beating
几分钟\Nfor a few minutes.
幸好我还有备用的\NLuckily
我一直没机会谢谢你当年救了我\NI never got to thank you... for saving my life.
我当时才六岁\NI-I was six.
我没帮到你什么\NI hardly did anything.
别人冷酷无情时  你却宽容相待\NYou were kind... when everyone else was cruel.
这对我意义重大\NThat's something.
宵禁警告\NCurfew warning...
十分钟后就宵禁了  你们该走了\NCurfew starts in ten minutes; you guys should go.
宵禁警告  十...\NCurfew warning: ten...
我不敢相信当年棚屋里的男孩就是他\NI can't believe that was him
不过他显然已经长大了\NBut
朱莉娅\NJulia...
我很抱歉\NI'm sorry.
你在隔离区肯定\NCome on
有男友吧\Nback in the Sector
我真没有\NNo. There's nobody.
谁会想到奥特里安人能这么性感\NWho knew an Atrian could be so sexy?
你是校园里的话题女王\NYou're the talk of the school.
不过别告诉你的朋友泰瑞\NOh
因为我们觉得她可能会咬人\N'cause we think she might bite.
我该去上课了\NI should get to class.
你去哪里  你去哪里\NWhere you going? Where you going?
跟我说说\NHey
有关歪星人的传言是真的吗\Nis it true what they say about Tatties?
别碰我\NOh... Don't!
你性子还挺烈的嘛\NWell
-别碰我  -喂  你\N- Stop it! - Hey! Hey!
离她远点\NLeave her alone.
你非得碍我的事是吧\NYou just can't seem to get out of my way
她是我妹妹\NThat's my sister.
那好\NOkay.
罗曼\NRoman!
-来人啊  -放开他\N- Help! - Get off him!
放开他\NHey
谁来帮帮他\NSomebody help him!
别打了  别再打了\NHey! Hey
滚吧\NGet out of here!
滚回你的垃圾星球去吧\NGo back to your own damn planet!
快让他滚\NHey
我观察你很久了  罗曼\NI've been watching you for a long time
我和你父亲一起\NI worked closely with your father
促成了这个项目\Nto help build this program.
你要是不想让它失败\NUnless you want to see it fail
就别像个野兽一样为所欲为\Nyou have to stop acting like an animal.
他攻击我妹妹  我却成了野兽\NHe assaulted my sister
要是这种事再次发生\NThis happens again
他们就会把你交给军医\Nthey'll hand you over to military doctors to have
用你的睾丸做实验\Nyour testicles put in a jar and studied.
你不想这样吧\NYou don't want that.
我也不想这样\NI don't want that.
我的睾丸也绝对不想\NAnd my testicles definitely don't want that.
我一向倾力保护我的投入\NI always protect my investments.
但前提是他们有生存能力\NThat is
罗曼\NRoman.
今晚你会来吧\NYou're coming tonight
没错  格雷森  你会看到她的\NYes
拜托  能洒脱一点吗\NGod. Attempt to be cool.
连像埃默里这样的社交新人\NEven social newbies like Emery
都还是喜欢那些暗恋者不要太过主动\Nstill like a little cool with their drool.
C区清人检查\NQuadrant C cleared for inspection.
不用你管  泰瑞\NStay out of it
就算你能闯进他们的烂派对\NEven if you can get out to crash their lame party
你也不可能在宵禁之前赶回来\Nyou'll never get back in time to make curfew.
不试试看怎么知道\NMaybe
我们得给他们点颜色看看\NBut we need to send a message
不能让今天罗曼的事再重演\NWhat happened to Roman today can never happen again.
都开始穿高跟鞋了\NHigh heels now?
要去约会了\NIt's the beginning of the end.
去参加派对而已\NNo
多加小心\NYou'll be careful?
一向如此\NAlways.
玩得开心点\NHave fun.
你该好好放松一下了\NYou deserve it.
我要去隔离区了\NI'm out of here. Off to the Sectoec
老爸再见\NBye
你想念它吗\NDo you ever miss it?
想念什么\NWhat?
奥特里安吗\NAtria?
当然\NOf course.
没有一天不想\NEvery day.
但是\NBut...
如今这里才是我们的家\Nthis is our home now.
武装守卫\NArmed guards
强制宵禁  还有铁丝网\Nmandatory curfew and barbed wire.
我印象里的家可不是这样的\NIt's not exactly my idea of home.
不会一成不变的\NIt won't be like that forever.
老爸  他们\NDad
他们不会平等对待我们的\Nthey're never gonna treat us like equals.
你们这代人会消除隔阂的\NYou know
有隔阂也是他们造成的\NA gap they created.
我不是说这一切能立马实现\NI-I'm not saying it's gonna happen tomorrow.
这需要时间\NThese things take time.
但我相信他们\NBut I have faith in them.
就如同我相信你一样\NJust like I have faith in you.
你跟其他人不一样\NYou're not like the rest.
我看不到希望\NI just don't see it.
我们明天再接着种吧\NWe'll finish this planting tomorrow.
怎么了  泰瑞\NWhat do you want
我看到你昨晚\NI saw you last night
和那个叫埃默里的女孩在一起\Nwith that girl Emery.
我只是帮她脱离困境\NI was keeping her out of trouble.
我不明白你为什么要费心和他们来往\NI don't know why you even bother making connections with them.
他们很快就会被隔离起来了\NSoon
你这话是什么意思\NWhat are you talking about?
我妈和其他人\NJust something my mother
在他们的周一聚会上这么说的\Nand the rest of the Trags talk about in their Monday meeting.
无意冒犯  泰瑞  但你妈屁也不懂\NNo offense
顺便说一句\NOh
德雷克他们去找那个埃里克了\NDrake and them went after that kid Eric.
一级防范禁闭  2200小时\NLockdown
我想要溜出去\NI'm looking for the path to Hades.
你不是诺克斯的儿子吗\NAren't you Nox's son?
你一定是认错人了\NYou must be confused.
能帮我吗\NCan you help?
就像我跟你朋友说的那样\NAs I told your friends
在标记重新启动之前\Nyou've got three hours
你只有三个小时\Nbefore the signal reactivates.
B区8号走廊\NZone B. Corridor 8.
找到那盏坏掉的灯\NLook for the broken light.
正下方有一块假墙板\NDirectly beneath
好了\NOkay.
我不得不动粗才从一个新生那里搞到\NI had to strong-arm a freshman to get the last
最后一点蓝色潘趣\Nof the blue punch.
谢谢\NThanks.
干杯\NCheers.
你还好吧\NYou all right?
当然了\NYeah. Sure.
你看上去有些心不在焉\NYou just seem a little distracted.
这一切对我来说\NThis is all just...
太新鲜了\Npretty new to me.
要试着放松  没人会说你闲话的\NJust try to relax. You're not being judged.
这里的大多数人都自恋得很\NMost people here are too self-obsessed
才不会关心别人呢\Nto care about anyone else.
大家快来看啊\NHey! You guys got to see this!
看看他们对布洛克干了什么\NLook what someone did to Brock!
谁干的\NWho did this?
谁干的\NWho did this?!
我们只想谈谈\NWe just want to have a little talk.
好吧\NAll right.
今晚得做个了结\NThis ends tonight.
只此一次  我同意\NFor once
我们受够了\NWe're sick of it!
你们这群人每天都来找我们麻烦\NYou guys messing with us every day!
都结束了  如果你们再纠缠我们\NIt's done! It's over! This is what's gonna happen
这就是你们的下场  听明白了吗\Nif you keep messing with us
住手\NHey! Come on!
罗曼  你来干什么\NRoman
你知道他们发现你们出了隔离区\NDo you know what they'd do to you
会拿你怎么样吗\Nif they found you outside the Sector?
你应该和我一条战线\NYou should be fighting alongside of me
而不是和我对着干\Ninstead of against me!
警察\NCops!
快跑\NCome on!
罗曼  罗曼  罗...\NRoman. Roman! Ro...!
-你没事吧  -埃默里  快走\N- Are you okay? - Emery
快来  罗曼  上车\NCome on! Roman
你疯了吗  埃默里  别管他了\NAre you nuts? Come on
警察来了怎么办\NBut what about the cops?!
那是他的问题  不关我们的事  快走\NHis problem
埃默里  你要干什么  走啊\NEmery
-埃默里  -格雷森  我们必须离开\N- Emery! - Grayson
罗曼  快跑  跑比较快\NRoman
-我们不能丢下她  -当然可以\N- We can't just leave her! - Yes
她简直是个疯子\NShe's a total freak!
伙计  她选择了那个歪星人\NDude
认了吧\NOwn it.
快点  我们走\NCome on! Let's go!
你还好吗\NAre you okay?
除了刚才社交自杀了一把\NOther than having possibly just committed social suicide?
社交自杀  指躲开人群  避免社交活动
还好\NSure.
你呢\NYou okay?
真好笑\NYou know
这么多年来我父亲一直在教我\NAll these years
那被称道的所谓"人性"\Nabout this vaunted thing called "Humanity
从定义上来说  那是我们\Nsomething that
不可能拥有的\Nwe could never possess.
但是...\NBut...
和你们人类接触了几天之后\Nafter spending just a few days amongst your kind...
我弄不明白"人性"这个概念了\Nthis concept of "Humanity" doesn't seem so clear to me.
不是的  世上还是有很多好人的\NNo. There are a lot of good people out there.
是吗\NYeah?
我只遇见过一个\NWell
你不必害怕\NYou don't have to be afraid.
对不起\NSorry.
是我妈\NIt's my mom.
我一会儿就到家\NI'll be home soon.
好的  我正在路上\NO-Okay. I'm on my way.
是...朱莉娅\NIt's... Julia.
我得走了\NI have to go.
我明白\NI understand.
继续往前直走\NIf you keep walking straight
你就会找到回隔离区的路\Nyou'll find the road to the Sector.
谢谢你\NThanks.
你没事吧\NAre you okay?
我得走了\NI have to go.
泰瑞\NTeri.
几小时前你和罗曼在一起\NYou were with Roman a few hours ago.
你知道他现在在哪里吗  都快宵禁了\NDo you know where he is? It's almost curfew.
泰瑞\NTeri?
你怎么能让我儿子出去\NHow could you let my son go out there?
先生们  出什么事了\NIs there a problem here
没事\NNo
离开桌子  让我看到你们的手\NStep away from the table. Let me see your hands.
那是什么\NWhat's that?
这可不行  威布尔\NNot good
放下武器\NDrop your weapon!
威布尔  不要\NWeeble
有人中枪\NMan down!
怀特希尔指挥官\NCommander Whitehill!
雷\NRay!
你没事吧\NAre you okay?
星恋